Any entertainment there?
All right. Here we go! 1999,the year of Joey.
來羅！1999年 喬伊「快樂」的一年
We're very happy for you.
恭喜你
What's the matter?
怎麼了？
We wanted to kiss at midnight, but nobody else will,so....
我們想在午夜接吻 但其他人都沒這個打算
All right,I'll take care of it.
好，交給我
It's 30 seconds to midnight, what are you gonna do?
喬伊，只剩30秒了 你能怎麼辦？
Will you just trust me?
相信我好嗎？
Thirty-three, 32, 31
33！32！31
Who are you kissing at midnight? Rachel or Phoebe?
你0點要親誰？ 瑞秋還是菲比？
You can't kiss your sister.
你又不能親你妹
-Who's gonna kiss my sister? -Chandler.
那誰要親我妹？ 錢德
Oh,man! Really?
不會吧
Would you rather have me or him kiss her?
老兄，你覺得誰比較好 我還是錢德？
That's a good point.
有道理
Since I have that whole history with Rachel,I guess Phoebe.
我和瑞秋有太多糾葛 那就菲比吧
Phoebe! Listen. Ross wants to kiss you at midnight.
菲比！羅斯午夜想親你
So obvious. Why doesn't he just ask?
太明顯了，他大可直說
-Rach! I'm gonna kiss you at midnight. -What?
瑞秋！我午夜要親你 什麼？
You can't kiss Ross. You got the history.
你親羅斯會小尷尬
So?
所以呢？
-Would you prefer me or Chandler? -Good point.
所以你想讓我親還是讓錢德親 有道理 對吧
Three, two, one!
3！2！1！
Happy New Year!
新年快樂！
-Happy New Year. -Happy New Year.
新年快樂
-Happy New Year. -You too.
菲比，新年快樂 你也是
Happy New Year,Joey.
喬伊，新年快樂
So that do anything for you?
剛才那個吻如何？
The One with All the Resolutions
本集播出：「新年新希望」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
You know what?
你們知道嗎？
I'm gonna go out on a limb and say "No divorces in '99!"
我要召告天下 99年我不離婚
But your divorce isn't final yet.
但你的離婚手續還沒辦好
Just the one divorce in '99!
99年我只離一次婚 漂亮
I am gonna be happy this year. I am gonna make myself happy.
我今年要過得很快樂 我要讓自己快樂
Do you want us to leave the room?
你要我們迴避嗎？
Every day I am gonna do one thing I have never done before.
我每天都要做一件沒做過的事
That is my New Year's resolution.
這就是我的新年新希望
That's a good one!
好棒的希望
Mine is to pilot a commercial jet.
我是想開大型客機
Now you only have to find a planeload of people...
這個也很棒，接著你得找一群
...whose resolution is to plummet to their deaths.
希望自己墜機身亡的人
Maybe your resolution should be not to make fun of your friends.
也許你應該立志不取笑朋友
Especially the ones who might fly you to Europe for free.
尤其是會免費載你去歐洲的人
She has a better chance of flying up your nose...
她開飛機的機率
...than you do of not making fun of us.
比你不取笑我們還高
I'll bet $50 you can't go the year without making fun of us.
50元賭你無法1年不笑我們
Better yet,a week.
乾脆1星期好了
I'll take that bet,my friend.
我賭了
Paying me the $50 can be...
輸我那50元 就可以當你的...
...the "new thing you do" that day.
「每日新鮮事」
And it starts right now!
就從現在開始
My New Year's resolution is to learn how to play guitar.
我的新年新希望是學吉他
Really? How come?
真的？為什麼？
You know those special skills I have listed on my resume?
我的履歷表 不是列了一堆特殊專長
I would love it if one of those was true.
我希望有一項是真的
Want me to teach you? I'm a great teacher.
你要我教你嗎？ 我是個很好的老師
Really? Who have you taught?
真的？你教過誰？
Well, I taught me. And I loved me.
我教過我，我很喜歡我
That'd be great! Yeah, thanks, Phoebe.
太好了，謝謝你
My resolution is to be less obsessed with being neat and clean.
我希望自己不要那麼潔癖
Really?
是嗎？
No!
不要
Or something else.
換一個好了
Look. Blaire forgot her glasses.
布萊兒忘了把眼鏡帶走
She'll need these to keep an eye on that boyfriend.
她需要這副眼鏡來盯住男朋友
Who,from what I hear, needs to keep his stapler...
聽說他得把訂書機...
...in his desk drawer, if you know what I mean!
...收在收屜裡 你們懂我的意思吧
Maybe your resolution should be to gossip less.
或許你應該讓自己別那麼八卦
What? I don't gossip.
我哪有八卦
Maybe sometimes I find out things.
或許我偶爾會發現一些事
Or I hear something and I pass that information on.
或聽到一些事，然後轉述出去
You know, kind of like a public service.
當做一種服務
It doesn't mean I'm a gossip. Is Ted Koppel a gossip?
這並不代表我很八卦 你們會說新聞主播八卦嗎？
If Ted Koppel talked about his coworkers' botched boob jobs, I would.
如果他說同事隆胸失敗的話
They were like this!
她隆成這樣耶
Fine, my New Year's resolution will be not to gossip.
好，我的新年新希望 就是不八卦
-It's easy. -Easy? You have never kept a resolution.
這還不簡單 簡單？你從來沒做到過
-Yes, I have. -Okay, let's see how you did last year.
我當然有 好，來看看你去年的表現
No. No. Not my diary. You cannot read my diary.
不要拿我的日記 你不能看我的日記
"Dear diary: I'm so excited.
親愛的日記：我好興奮
My resolution is to write in you every day. See you tomorrow."
我的新年新希望是每天寫你 我們明天見
Nothing.
什麼都沒寫
You know,not a lot happened last year.
去年發生了很多事
All right,I will prove to you that I can keep it this time. No more gossiping.
好，我這次會證明給你們看 我再也不八卦了
I hate gossip. In junior high this girl said a lot of mean stuff about me...
講到八卦，國中時 有個女生說了我很多壞話
...and I set her bike on fire.
我就放火燒她的腳踏車
-Wow,what did she say about you? -She said I was crazy.
她說你什麼？ 她說我是瘋子
But I guess she got hers.
得到報應了吧
「中央咖啡館」
-I'll see you tomorrow. -Okay.
那就明天見 好
I just asked that girl out.
我約剛才那個女生出去
Nice!
漂亮
Is that part of your "new thing" for today?
這算是你今天的新鮮事嗎？
Yes, it is. See?
沒錯，你們看
"Elizabeth...
伊麗莎白…
...Hornswoggle"?
宏史歪哥？
That's right.
對…
Elizabeth Hornswoggle.
伊麗莎白宏史歪哥
Horn..swoggle
宏史歪哥
You okay,Chandler?
你還好嗎？
Something funny about that name?
這個姓有哪裡好笑嗎？
No, I just think I've heard it somewhere before.
沒有，我只是覺得好像聽過
Oh, really? Where?
是嗎？在哪裡聽過？
Somewhere funny,I'll bet.
一定是個很好笑的地方
Guess what.
你猜怎麼著
I have a date with Elizabeth Hornswoggle.
我要跟一個伊麗莎白… 宏史歪哥約會
Hornswoggle. Oh, this must be killing you!
宏史歪哥？ 你的嘴一定很癢
Not really.
才不會
-I haven't told you her middle name yet. -Well,don't. Just don't.
我還沒說她中間的名字 拜託 不要
-See you later. -See you.
待會見
All right, Phoebe, I am ready for my first lesson.
菲比，我可以上第一課了
No, you don't touch the guitar.
不行，不能碰吉他
First you learn here, then here.
先練手，再練琴
Okay.
好吧
Lesson one: Chords.
好，第一課，和弦
Now,I don't know the actual names of the chords.
我不知道這些和弦的真正名稱
But I made up names for the way my hand looks while I'm doing them.
不過我照手勢幫它們取了名字
So then this is "Bear Claw."
所以這是熊爪…
"Turkey Leg"...
火雞腳…
...and "Old Lady."
和老太太
What an interesting approach to guitar instruction.
真有趣的吉他教學方式
You know,some might find it amusing. I myself find it regular.
有些人可能會覺得好笑 我覺得很普通
Hey, everybody!
各位
Rachel was so good today. She didn't gossip at all.
瑞秋今天很乖 她都沒有八卦
I didn't. Even when I found out
沒錯，即使我發現…
Let's say I found out something about someone...
總之我發現了某人的某件事
...and let's just say...
但是...
...she's gonna keep it.
...我不會說出來
Check this out.
菲比，你看
You nailed the Old Lady!
你搞定老太太了
I thought I was getting better, so I stopped by this guitar store
我覺得我進步了 就在回家的路上去吉他店…
Did you touch any of the guitars there?
你在店裡有碰吉他嗎？
Did you?
有嗎？
No.
沒有
Give me your hands.
手給我
Strings. This
琴弦，這一隻
Pick.
彈片
-Do you want to learn to play guitar? -Yes.
你想學吉他嗎？ 想啊
Then don't touch one!
那就不要碰吉他
-Hi,Ben. -Auntie Monica!
班 摩妮卡姑姑
Ross is wearing leather pants!
羅斯穿皮褲
Does nobody else see Ross is wearing leather pants?
沒有人看見羅斯穿皮褲嗎？
Someone comment on the pants!
誰來說句話吧
-I think they're very nice. -I really like them a lot.
很帥氣啊 我很喜歡
Not what I had in mind.
我想的不是這個
People like Ross don't wear these types of pants.
羅斯這種人通常不穿這種褲子
You see, they're very tight.
這種褲子很緊
Maybe there's something in that area?
也許可以評論一下
I think they look really good.
很好看啊
Where'd you get them?
在哪裡買的？
I needed a new thing for today.
我還沒做今天的新鮮事
There's this leather store that always smells so good.
我一直覺得這家皮衣店很香
And I thought to myself:  "Wow. I've never owned...
於是我心想 我從來沒買過...
...a really good-smelling pair of pants before."
...一條很香的皮褲
Oh,come on!
拜託啦！
What do you think?
說真的，你們覺得怎樣？
You look like a freak.
好怪
Awful!
難看死了
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
-It's my New Year's resolution. -To blind my child?
這是我的新年新希望 把我兒子弄瞎？
To take pictures of us together.
不，是多照照我們的相片
It's the best resolution. Everyone can enjoy them.
我覺得這樣最好 大家都會喜歡
Everyone will enjoy my music as well.
大家也都會喜歡我的演奏
My God,these pants! I'm burning up.
天哪，這條褲子熱死了
Oh God! She wants to snuggle now? Is she trying to kill me?
她現在靠過來是想讓我死嗎？
It's like a volcano in here!
這裡面跟火山一樣
-Are you hot? -No.
你熱嗎？ 不會
It must just be me, then.
那就是我在熱
That was just the pants and the couch.
那是褲子跟沙發磨擦的聲音
Do you mind if I use your bathroom?
可以借用一下洗手間嗎？
-Go ahead. -Thanks.
請便 謝謝
My favorite part's coming up!
我最喜歡的部分要來了 好
Oh,my God!
完蛋了
Tiger.
老虎
Dragon.
恐龍
Iceberg!
冰山
Joseph, did you even study at all last night?
喬瑟夫，你昨晚有練習嗎？
Yes,I did!
我有啊
Then do lceberg.
那就把冰山做出來
G-sharp.
升C
G-sharp?
升C？
Have you been studying the real names of the chords?
你在偷學和弦名稱嗎？
Have you?
有沒有？
Oh,my God!
我的天哪
What? I didn't touch a guitar!
怎樣？我又沒有碰吉他
But you're questioning my method!
但是你質疑我的教學方式
No, I'm not questioning it. I'm saying it's stupid!
我不是質疑 我根本就覺得很蠢
What?
幹嘛？
Thank you.
謝謝
You know, none of my other student...
其他學生...
...thought I was stupid.
...都不覺得我蠢
Your other student was you!
你的其他學生就是你
Well, maybe you just need to try a little harder!
那又怎樣，也許你應該更用功
Maybe I need to try a real teacher!
也許我應該找個正牌老師
Here! Andy Cooper. He teaches guitar.
這裡，安迪古柏，他在教吉他
There's a picture of him with a kid.
這裡還有他跟小朋友的合照
And the kid's got a guitar!
小朋友拿著吉他
Fine!
好，
You learn from your "qualified instructor."
你去跟你的專業老師學
But don't come crying when everyone is sick...
不過你可別哭著來找我
...of hearing you play "Bad,Bad Leroy Brown"!
等大家聽膩了「壞蛋李洛布朗」
全城最壞的大壞蛋
Oh,fine. Take his side!
好啊，你去幫他啊
I can't wait to be with you.
我好想趕快去找你
I'll sneak over as soon as I can.
羅斯把小孩接走我就溜過去
I'll tell Rachel I'll be doing laundry.
我會告訴瑞秋 我要洗兩個小時衣服
Laundry. Is that my new nickname?
洗衣服？那是我的新綽號嗎？
You know what your nickname is, Mr. Big
你明知你的綽號是大雕
Would you stop looking at me like that? Phoebe was a terrible teacher.
別再那樣看我了 菲比是個爛老師
I wasn't learning anything from her
我什麼都沒學到
Look I feel bad, too Forget it, we're going around in circles.
我也很難過… 算了，講來講去都一樣
走開啦
Joey, it's Ross. I need some help.
喬伊，我是羅斯，我需要幫忙
Chandler's not here.
錢德不在
You can help me.
你可以幫我
Okay.
好
Listen, I'm in Elizabeth's bathroom.
我在伊麗莎白的浴室裡
Nice!
漂亮
No, I got really hot in my pants, so I took them off.
不是，我覺得皮褲很熱 就進來脫掉
But they must have shrunk from the sweat.
結果它一定是遇汗縮水
Or my legs expanded from the heat.
或是我的腿因熱膨脹
I can't get them back on, Joey. I can't!
我現在穿不回去了
That is quite a situation.
這個情況蠻嚴重的
Do you see any powder?
你有粉之類的東西嗎？
Powder! Yeah, I have powder.
有，我有爽身粉
Good, good.
很好
Sprinkle some on. It'll absorb moisture.
把它撒在腿上吸汗
Then you can get your pants on.
就能把褲子穿回去了
Yeah,hold on.
好，等一下
They're not coming on,man.
褲子還是拉不上來
Okay,cut slits in the pants, right? Then put them back on...
好，把褲子割破幾刀再穿回去
...go out there and tell her you're the lncredible Hulk.
然後出去告訴她你是綠巨人
Chandler's not there?
錢德不在是吧？
That would have worked, but all right,fine.
那樣真的可以，不過算了
You see any.... Oh,Vaseline?
你找得到凡士林嗎？
I see lotion. I have lotion. Will that work?
我找到乳液，我有乳液 乳液行嗎？
Sure, throw some of that on there.
行，把它塗在腿上 等一下
Hold on.
Sounds like it's working.
聽起來有用
They're still not coming on,man.
褲子還是拉不上來
And the lotion and the powder have made a paste.
而且乳液和爽身粉糊成一團
Really.
是喔？
What color is it?
什麼顏色？
What difference does that make?
什麼顏色有差嗎？
If the paste matches the pants, you can make paste pants...
如果跟褲子的顏色一樣 你就糊一條假褲子
...and she won't know!
她就看不出來了
Do you have a minute?
喬伊，你有空嗎？
Dude, what am l
我該怎麼…
Rachel's here, so good luck. Let me know how it goes.
瑞秋來了，祝你好運 讓我知道結果
Joey,I have such a problem.
喬伊，我遇到天大的問題
Your timing couldn't be better.
你來得正好
I'm putting out fires all over the place.
我正在到處救火
Okay. Joey, I have got to tell you something.
好，喬伊，我得告訴你一件事
What is it?
什麼事？
Oh，my God！ It's so huge! But promise me. You cannot tell anyone.
天哪，這件事太大條了 但你得保證不說出去
No,no,no! I don't want to know.
不要，我不想知道
You do want to know. This is unbelievable!
你絕對想知道，太不可思議了
I'm tired of being the guy who knows all the secrets...
我不管，我不想再當知道秘密...
...and can't tell anyone.
...卻不能說的人
You know secrets?
什麼秘密？你知道什麼秘密？
You're not supposed to gossip!
你不該八卦的
I know. I just can't keep this in. So I pick up the phone
我知道，但這件事我憋不住 我剛才拿起電話…
I'm not listening to you!
我不聽
You've been in there for a long time.
羅斯，你進去很久了
I'm starting to get kind of freaked out.
我開始有點害怕了
All right, I'm coming out.
好，我要出去了
Hey,can you turn the lights off?
你可以把燈關掉嗎？
Let's just leave the lights on.
不行，燈就讓它開著
Oh,my God!
我的天哪
I had a problem.
我出了一點狀況
I can't talk to you. I don't have a fancy ad in the yellow pages.
我不能跟你說話 我沒在電話簿上登廣告
Look, Phoebe, I just...
菲比，你聽我說…
I want to apologize for saying your method was stupid.
我為批評你的教法道歉
And maybe ask you to be my teacher again?
我也想重新拜你為師
I promise,I won't touch a guitar until you say I'm ready.
在你說可以之前 我絕對不碰吉他
You really think I'm ready?
我真的可以了？
Wow,cool!
酷斃了
-Was the chord at least right before? -No.
那個和弦彈對了嗎？ 不對
Oh,my God!
殺了我吧
We heard about your pants. I'm so sorry.
我們聽說了，好慘
This year was supposed to be great.
今年應該很美好才對
It's only the second day and I'm a loser...
才第二天我就成了...
...with stupid leather pants that don't even fit!
...穿不合身的皮褲的遜人
You're not a loser.
沒這回事 你不遜
Look at me!
你們看我
Hey,look!
你看
Ben drew a picture of you.
班畫了你的畫像
You're a cowboy.
你是牛仔喔
Because of the leather pants?
因為我穿皮褲？
He thinks you're a cowboy, not a loser. That's something.
班並不覺得你遜 他覺得你是牛仔，很棒吧
-lt really is something. -Howdy,partner.
真的很棒 牛仔哥
Maybe I should get another pair.
也許我應該再去買一條
You know,they had some...
他們有一些...
...with fringe all down the sides.
...側邊有流蘇的
Phoebe,you may know this. You know strange things.
菲比，這種怪事你可能會知道
What is the boiling point of brain?
腦漿的沸點是幾度？
I used to know this.
我以前知道
I'm gonna go kiss Ben good night.
我去跟班說晚安
I can't believe he thinks I'm a cowboy.
他居然覺得我是牛仔
I would make a good cowboy.
我會是個好牛仔
Now that everything's wrapped up, I'll do my laundry.
好，既然沒事 我要去洗衣服了
Yeah,me too. If this shirt is dirty.
我也是，如果這一件髒了的話
I'm going to the airport.
我要去機場
If I hang around there long enough...
只要等久一點
...someone's bound to leave a plane unattended.
應該能逮到沒人管的飛機
-Good luck,honey. -Bye.
祝你好運 再見
Remember that thing I was gonna tell you about?
喬伊 記得我要說的那件大事嗎？
I won't tell you. But if you found out on your own...
我不會告訴你 但如果你自己發現
...that would be okay and we could talk about it.
那就沒關係 我們就可以討論了對吧？
Well,then it wouldn't be a secret. So that would be okay.
那樣就不是秘密，的確沒關係
Would you mind going into Chandler's bedroom...
喬伊，你去錢德的房間
...and getting that book he borrowed from me?
把我借給他的書拿回來好嗎？
Now? You want me to go over there now?
現在？你要我現在去？
-Do you know something? -Do you know something?
你知道什麼嗎？ 你知道什麼？
-I might know something. -I might know something too.
我或許知道 我也是
-What do you know? -You tell me first.
你知道什麼？ 不行，你先說我才能說
-I can't. -Then I can't.
我不能說 那我也不能說
Okay,fine.
那好吧
You don't know.
你才不知道
I'll walk into his bedroom and see the thing...
不如我現在就去錢德的房間
...I think I know is actually the thing I think I know!
就可以知道我想的確實沒錯
-You know! -And you know!
你知道 你也知道
Yeah,I know!
對，我知道
Chandler and Monica? Oh,this is unbelievable!
錢德和摩妮卡？ 真叫人不敢相信
-How long have you known? -Too long!
你知道多久了？ 太久了
I've been dying to talk to someone about this!
天哪，我早就想找人說了
You can't say anything to anybody. They're so weird about that.
聽著，我們不能告訴別人 他們兩個好緊張…
It's raining.
下雨了
I don't like to fly in the rain.
我不想在下雨天飛
I am gonna go for a walk in the rain.
我要去雨中漫步
Me too.
我也要
That's weird.
怪人
I bet they're doing it.
他們一定有一腿
Okay,look. I can't take it anymore.
好，我憋不住受不了了
So you win. Okay? Here.
你贏，好嗎？拿去
Flying a jet? Make it a spaceship...
菲比，開飛機？ 不如開太空船...
...so you can get back to your home planet!
...回你的星球去
Phone call for you. Tom Jones. He wants his pants back!
羅斯，有你的電話 湯姆瓊斯跟你要他的褲子
And Hornswoggle? What, are you dating a character from Fraggle Rock?
宏史歪哥？ 你在跟卡通人物約會嗎？